jossandmain.com 2015-09-05

# Joss and Main - Curated Flash Sales for Furniture and Décor

This Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") is designed to help you understand how Wayfair LLC and its affiliated brands, including Wayfair.com, Joss & Main, DwellStudio, AllModern and Wayfair Supply ("Joss and Main", "Wayfair", "we" or "us" ) collects and processes the information that you share when you use this and any of our websites (together, the "Site") and our mobile application (the "App," and together with the Site, the "Service"). 

Before submitting information to the Service, please review this Privacy Policy carefully. By using or accessing the Service, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you prefer that we not collect and process information about you, please do not provide it to us and do not access the Service. 

We do not knowingly collect any Personal Information from children under 13. Where any such information is inadvertently collected, we will delete the information as soon as possible. If you believe a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. 

Information We Collect 

We collect the information that you share with us, including: 

  * Personal Information: "Personal Information" is information that can personally identify you, such as your name, email address and telephone number. We maintain one or more databases to store your Personal Information and may retain it as reasonably required to serve you and operate the Service. Personal Information that we collect depends on how you use the Service. Providing your Personal Information to us is your choice. If you choose not to provide us with certain Personal Information, you may not be able to take advantage of certain features of the Service; and 
  * General Information: When you visit the Service, we may collect various categories of general non-personal information ("General Information"). General Information includes browser information, operating system information, device information, TCP-IP address and the date, time, length of stay and specific pages accessed during your visits to the Service. 

Registering for the Service 

If you register to use the Service, we may collect Personal Information including your name, email address, and telephone number. 

You may also register for the Service using another service, such as Facebook. If you create your Wayfair account by connecting through another service, you are authorizing us to use public information from that connected account to help complete your Wayfair profile. Please remember that the manner in which the service uses, stores, and discloses your information is governed solely by the policies of such service. We recommend that you review the terms and policies of that service, including its privacy and data gathering practices. Wayfair shall have no liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of any third party service provider or any other third-party site or service that may be enabled within the Service. 

You may review, update, or modify your account information, including profile and contact information, at any time by logging into your Wayfair account. You may also permanently delete your account by contacting us. 

Online Identification Tools 

Like many website providers, we use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and provide a better web experience. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and gather General Information. 

We use web beacons (a.k.a. clear GIFs, web bugs or pixel tags) to personalize your experience of the Service and to generate information about Service traffic and trends. Web beacons collect General Information, such as the type of browser that you use and your IP address. Web beacons may be used alone or in conjunction with cookies; when web beacons are used with cookies, they may link General Information to Personal Information. Web beacons usually are not visible to you. 

We also use cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and for other purposes like personalizing the Service. A cookie is a small file stored by your internet browser on your computer. A "session cookie" stores temporary information that is erased when you close your web browser or turn off your computer. A "persistent cookie" enables the Service to recognize you when ou return to it and remains stored on your computer until you delete it. Your web browser is usually set up to initially accept cookies. If you set your browser to reject cookies, the Service will not be able to recognize your account or to personalize the content that you see. A "flash cookie," also known as a "local storage object," is not stored in your browser, unlike other cookies, and instead placed on your computer by websites that use Adobe Flash. You may disable flash cookies via your Flash Player preferences or by using third-party software. We do not and cannot use cookies to gather other information that may be stored on your hard drive. 

Third-party advertising management partners may help us display tailored content to our customers’ interests and serve interest-based advertising on our behalf. Wayfair and our advertising management partners may use cookies, web beacons and other tools to collect General Information about your activities on the Service, to deliver advertising on the Service or elsewhere on the Internet based upon your interests that may be more relevant to you and to measure effectiveness of our marketing efforts and the Service. 

You may "opt out" of receiving some interest-based advertisements by following the instructions at www.aboutads.info/choices or www.networkadvertising.org/choices/. (An "opt-out cookie" will be placed on your computer indicating that you do not want to receive interest-based advertisements. If you delete cookies on your computer, you will need to opt-out again.) You may opt out of certain interest-based advertisements that use Wayfair.com's cookie by clicking [here](http://dtmc.wayfair.com/adinfo/choice/prod/?type=fpc&cid=2416&cname=Wayfair&cmagic=5dec70&clogo=csn_wayfair.png&loc=us&lang=en-us). You may opt out of certain interest-based advertisements that use AllModern.com's cookie by clicking [here](http://dtmc.allmodern.com/adinfo/choice/prod/?type=fpc&cid=2512&cname=All%20Modern&cmagic=831caa&clogo=AllModern_2013.png&loc=us&lang=en-us). To learn more about cookies in general, including how to manage and delete cookies, visit www.allaboutcookies.org. 

Opting out of receiving interest-based advertisements through the links above does not mean you will no longer see digital advertisements from Wayfair or our ad management partners; rather, opting out means that most of the digital advertisements that you do see will not be based on your particular interests. In addition, certain data collection tools on the Service (including cookies) still may collect information about your use of the Service, such as for analytics and fraud prevention. 

How We Respond to Do Not Track Signals 

Some web browsers (including Safari, Internet Explorer, Firefox and Chrome) incorporate a "Do Not Track" ("DNT") or similar feature that signals to websites that a user does not want to have his or her online activity and behavior tracked. If a website that responds to a particular DNT signal receives the DNT signal, the browser can block that website from collecting certain information about the browser's user. Not all browsers offer a DNT option and DNT signals are not yet uniform. For this reason, many digital service operators, including Wayfair, do not recognize or respond to DNT signals. 

Third Party Features 

The Service also may include an activity feed, social media buttons and widgets, such as the Facebook "Like" button or the "Share This" button. These features may collect and display your Personal Information, your IP address and the page you are visiting on the Service and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. These features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on the Service and your interactions with them are governed by the privacy policy of the third party that provides the feature. 

Use of Service via Mobile Device 

If you use the Service through your mobile device, we may collect your geo-location information to assist us in fulfilling your order. We will not share this information with third parties and will only use this information for the sole purpose of fulfilling your order. You may at any time prevent the Service from using your location by turning this option off at the device level. 

When you use the Service through your mobile device, we also collect device type and UUID, a unique identifier generated within the App, and store this information in log files. We use this information to provide you with the most up to date application and features, or to advertise or promote products or services to you that are applicable to your device type. 

Third-Party Links 

We may provide links to third-party websites that we do not own or control. We are not responsible for the information collection practices of any website that we do not own or control. We encourage you to review and understand the privacy practices of third-party websites before providing any information to or through them. 

How Your Personal Information is Used, Processed and Disclosed 

Except as specified in this Privacy Policy, Wayfair does not rent, sell, trade or disclose your Personal Information to third parties without your prior consent. Wayfair may, however, use, process and disclose Personal Information to: 

  * send information to customers about orders;
  * fulfill your orders;
  * process and collect your payments;
  * administer "Wayfair Rewards" and other customer loyalty programs;
  * send you promotional marketing material about Wayfair’s company and partners;
  * produce content for our activity feed feature;
  * customize, analyze, adjust and improve the Service to better meet your needs;
  * execute a sweepstakes, contest or other promotion;
  * enforce Wayfair’s agreements with you;
  * provide you with important administrative information regarding the Service, such as changes to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, rewards and loyalty programs and other policies;
  * prevent fraud and other prohibited or illegal activities; and
  * comply with potential requests of law enforcement or data protection agencies.

When possible, General Information may be combined and/or linked to Personal Information, in accordance with the purposes specified above. 

We may use your General Information and deidentified Personal Information to prepare anonymized, aggregated data about our users ("Anonymized Data"). We may provide third parties with Anonymized Data in describing the Service to prospective partners, advertisers and other third parties, and for all other lawful purposes. As communicated to third parties, the Anonymized Data does not include any information permitting the recipient to identify, locate or contact you. 

Third Party Service Providers 

Wayfair employs other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf, such as fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, serving ads on our behalf, providing search results and links, and processing credit card payments. These third-party service providers have access to Personal Information needed to perform their functions but may not use it for any other purpose. 

Acquisition of Wayfair 

Information about customers is considered an asset of Wayfair and, as such, may be transferred to another company as part of a merger or acquisition. 

Information Sharing for Marketing Purposes 

To provide you with information about products and services that may be useful to you, we may partner with select reputable organizations whose privacy policies we believe are consistent with ours. Such organizations may include other retailers and magazine publishers. Through these arrangements, we may share, exchange, cross-reference and/or rent your name and mailing address. 

If you do not want us to share your Personal Information with third parties for marketing purposes, please contact us. Immediately after your request has been processed, your information will no longer be shared with any third party for marketing purposes. 

Blogs, Reviews and Forums 

The Service also may from time to time offer publicly-accessible blogs, customer reviews or forums. Any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected and used by others who access them. To request removal of your Personal Information from blogs, customer reviews or forums, please contact us. Please note that in some cases we may be unable to remove your Personal Information. 

Inviting Others 

You may choose to invite someone else to use the Service by providing his or her name and email address. We may use this information to send invitations to such individuals, to track the results of such invitation referrals, and to confirm qualifying orders attributable to your registered account. Anyone who receives an email invitation to use the Service may opt out of receiving such emails in the future by following the opt-out instructions in the email. We take commercially reasonable steps to implement all opt-out requests promptly, but those who opt out may still receive communications from us as we process the opt-out request, or as required for order processing and other purposes. 

Retention of Personal Information 

Wayfair retains Personal Information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by applicable law. 

Accessing and Updating Your Personal Information and Preferences 

Modifying or Deleting Your Personal Information 

If you would like to modify or delete your Personal Information, please contact us with clear instructions about what you would like to be modified or deleted. We will respond to your request promptly. 

Changing Your Subscription Preferences 

If you tell us that you do not want us to use your Personal Information to contact you, Wayfair will respect your wishes. If you are a registered user, you may change your preferences to receive or not to receive email or other communications from us by logging in to your account and indicating those preferences on the "My Account" section of our Service. 

You may also instruct Wayfair to stop sending you emails, newsletters or other information by following the ‘unsubscribe’ instructions provided in the email. Wayfair may, however, continue to use your Personal Information to contact you to service your account or as otherwise authorized by law. Please note that if you use more than one name or e-mail address when communicating with Wayfair or using the Service, you may continue to receive communications from Wayfair to any name and/or email address not specified in your opt-out request. 

Information for Visitors From California and Outside of the United States 

California Residents 

California law permits individuals who provide Wayfair with Personal Information and who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To request this information, please contact us. 

Visitors from Outside of the United States 

The Service is hosted in the United States. If you are visiting the Service from outside the United States, your information may be transferred to, stored and processed in the United States in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable US laws. Please note that data protection and other applicable laws of the United States may not be as comprehensive as those laws or regulations in your country or may otherwise differ from the data protection or consumer protection laws in your country. By using the Service, you consent to transfer of your information to our facilities as described in this Privacy Policy. 

Information Security 

We have instituted reasonable safeguards to help ensure that information collected is secure. We also take reasonable steps to ensure that third parties who work with us to make the Site (including the software, applications and services provided on the Site) available to you agree to protect personal information that they must access in order to serve you and to honor your preferences about contacts you receive. 

When you send or otherwise transmit your sensitive information (such as your credit card number) to or though the Sites, your sensitive information is encrypted and protected with SSL, the current industry-standard encryption protocol. When you are on an SSL-protected page, a picture of a closed lock appears at the bottom or top of some web browsers. Another way to tell if you are on a secure page is to check the URL or address of the page. (Look in the address box or right-click on the page and select "Properties".) These secure SSL-encrypted pages have URLs that start with "https://" instead of "http://". 

Please understand, however, that it is possible for third parties to access information despite our efforts. Without limiting the terms of our Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy, you understand that we do not guarantee that your use of the Site and/or information provided by you will be private or secure and we are not responsible or liable to you for any lack of privacy or security you may experience. You are fully responsible for taking precautions and providing security measures best suited for your situation and intended use of the Site. You also understand that any information provided by you or collected by us or our agents in connection with your use of the Site will be used in the manner described in our Terms of Use. Please do not use the Site if you do not agree to the terms and conditions described in this Information Security section. 

If you have any questions about security of the Site, please contact us. 

Changes to our Privacy Policy 

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices. When we post modifications to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the "Last Updated" date at the top of this web page. The modified Privacy Policy will be effective immediately upon posting on the Service. Your continued use of the Service after the posting of the modified Privacy Policy constitutes your agreement to abide and be bound by it. If we make any material change, we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Service prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. If you object to any modification, your sole recourse is to stop using the Service. 

Questions About our Privacy Policy 

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or Wayfair generally, please contact us. You can also send us physical mail to:

Wayfair LLC  
Attention: Legal Department  
4 Copley Place, Floor 7  
Boston, MA 02116 

Joss and Main Giveaway Sweepstakes Official Rules 

**NO PURCHASE NECESSARY TO ENTER OR WIN. A PURCHASE DOES NOT INCREASE YOUR CHANCES OF WINNING. VOID WHERE PROHIBITED. Joss and Main Giveaway Sweepstakes ("Promotion") begins each week at 12:00:00 PM Eastern Time ("ET") on Monday and ends at 11:59:59 AM ET on the following Monday (the "Promotion Period"). For the avoidance of confusion, each Promotion Period or week is a separate and distinct Promotion.** _The computer clock of the Sponsor is the official time-keeping device in the Promotion._

**EACH ENTRANT HEREBY REPRESENTS AND WARRANTS THAT SUCH ENTRANT IS AT LEAST 18 YEARS OF AGE AND THAT SUCH ENTRANT HAS READ THESE OFFICIAL RULES AND IS FAMILIAR WITH AND AGREES TO ITS CONTENTS. IF ENTRANT IS NOT AT LEAST 18 YEARS OF AGE AND DOES NOT AGREE TO THESE OFFICIAL RULES, DO NOT PARTICIPATE IN THIS PROMOTION.**

**ELIGIBILITY:** The Promotion is open only to legal residents of the 50 United States and the District of Columbia (excludes Guam, Puerto Rico and all other U.S. territories and possessions), who are 18 years of age or older at the time of Promotion registration. Employees, officers and directors of Joss and Main (the "Sponsor"), and Sponsor's parent, affiliates, subsidiaries, and advertising, contest, fulfillment and marketing agencies (all of such entities (including, but not limited to, the Sponsor) are collectively referred to herein as the, "Promotion Parties"), their immediate families (parent, child, sibling & spouse and their respective spouses, regardless of where they reside) and persons living in the same households as such individuals (whether related or not) are not eligible to participate in the Promotion. By participating, you agree to these Official Rules and to the decisions of the Sponsor, which are final and binding in all respects. Void where prohibited by law, rule or regulation. All applicable federal, state and local laws and regulations apply. 

**HOW TO ENTER THE SWEEPSTAKES:** To enter the Promotion, you must submit your valid email address entry at https://www.jossandmain.com/giveaways/ (the "Web Site") by 11:59:59 AM ET on Monday during the Promotion Period. 

**Limit of one (1) entry per person, per email address during the Promotion Period.**

**PRIZES, DRAWINGS & ODDS OF WINNING:** A total of one (1) prize (the "Prize") will be selected in electronic, randomized drawings. The drawing for the Prize (described below) will be held on Monday each week during the Promotion Period. The drawing will be from all eligible entries received each day throughout the Promotion Period. The drawing will be conducted by Sponsor, whose decisions are final and binding in all matters relating to this Promotion. Odds of winning depend on the number of eligible entries received. 

**PRIZES:** One (1) Prize will be awarded for each Promotion. The Prize will consist of the following:   
Home goods product(s).    
For example, a Prize may include one or more of the following: 

  * Bedroom, Kitchen, Dining, Bathroom, Living Room or Accent Furniture
  * Home Entertainment, Home Office, or Game Room Furniture
  * Home Décor, Home Accents, Rugs, Mirrors
  * Lighting
  * Cookware, Bakeware, or Kitchen Appliances
  * Bedding and Bath products
  * Patio Furniture and Outdoor Cooking supplies
  * Home Improvement products
  * Baby and Kids furniture and products

Prize may include multiple home goods products. 

**The Approximate Retail Value ("ARV") of the Prize during a Promotion is up to $5,000.00**

_*For the Prize, the home goods products style, color and size are subject to in-stock availability. Any applicable taxes are the sole responsibility of the winner._

**WINNER NOTIFICATION:** Potential winner will receive Prize notification and prize claim information via email within forty-eight (48) hours after the Monday drawing, or as soon thereafter as reasonably practicable. Sponsor is not responsible for any change in entrant's telephone number, mailing address, and/or email. Prize won by an eligible entrant who is a minor in his or her state of residence may be awarded to a minor's parent or legal guardian who must sign and return all documents. Winner (or winner's parent/legal guardian if winner is a minor) will have seven (7) calendar days from time of receipt of winning notification to confirm that the notification has been received in order to claim his/her Prize. A potential winner is subject to verification, including verification of age. If such potential winner cannot be contacted within a reasonable time period, if the potential winner is ineligible, if any notification is returned undeliverable, or if the potential winner otherwise fails to fully comply with these Official Rules, he/she will forfeit that Prize and, if time permits, an alternate winner will be selected from among all remaining entries for that drawing. 

**GENERAL PRIZE CONDITIONS:** Prize will only be awarded by Sponsor upon potential winner's verification of eligibility (if requested by Sponsor), and compliance with these Official Rules and final approval by Sponsor. No prize substitution, cash equivalent of Prize, transfer or assignment of Prize is permitted, except by Sponsor which reserves the right to substitute a Prize with one of comparable or greater value, in its sole discretion. Prize is awarded "as is" with no warranty or guarantee, either express or implied. All Prize details are at Sponsor's sole discretion. Any and all warranties and/or guarantees on a Prize (if any) are subject to the respective manufacturers' terms therefore, and winner agrees to look solely to such manufacturers for any such warranty and/or guarantee. An unclaimed Prize will not be awarded. All federal, state, local, and other taxes on a Prize and any other costs and expenses associated with Prize acceptance and use not specified herein as being provided, are the sole responsibility of the applicable winner. A 1099 tax form will be issued where required. Notwithstanding anything herein, a potential Prize winner (or potential winner's parent/legal guardian if potential winner is a minor) may be required to complete and return an Affidavit of Eligibility and Liability/Publicity Release form within five (5) calendar days of attempted delivery of same. Non-compliance within this time period or return of any Prize/Prize notification as undeliverable may result in disqualification. All federal, state, municipal, provincial and local laws and regulations apply. 

**PUBLICITY RELEASE:** Except where prohibited or restricted by law and notwithstanding the fact that the winner may be required to sign a separate Affidavit of Eligibility and Liability/Publicity Release, winner's (and his/her parent/legal guardian if a winner is a minor) acceptance of Prize constitutes winner's agreement and consent for Sponsor to use and/or publish the winner's full name, city and state of residence, Promotion entry, and/or statements made by winner regarding the Promotion or Sponsor, winner's voice, photographs and other likeness, worldwide and in perpetuity for any and all purposes, including, but not limited to, advertising, trade and/or promotion on behalf of Sponsor, in any and all forms of media, now known or hereafter devised, including, but not limited to, print, TV, radio, electronic, cable or World Wide Web, without further limitation, restriction, compensation, notice, review or approval. 

**MISCELLANEOUS:** Entrants who do not follow all of the instructions, provide the required information in their entry form or the like, or abide by these Official Rules or other instructions of Sponsor may be disqualified. All Promotion entries become the property of Sponsor and will not be acknowledged or returned. Online entries will be considered to be entered by the authorized account holder of the e-mail address submitted at time of entry and he/she must comply with these Official Rules. The authorized account holder is deemed as the natural person who is assigned to an e-mail address by an Internet access provider, online service provider or other organization that is responsible for assigning e-mail addresses for the domain associated with the submitted e-mail address. 

**PRIVACY:** Personal information collected by Sponsor will be used for administration of the Promotion and awarding of a Prize and for potential research purposes. In addition, by entering, entrants and/or winner (and their parents/legal guardians if entrant/winner is a minor) agree to Sponsor's use of entrant's/winner's personal information as described in its Privacy Policy [here.](https://www.jossandmain.com/p/privacy_policy?b_is_mobile_app=) Please refer to Sponsor's privacy policy for important information regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information by Sponsor. 

**RELEASE:** By participating in the Promotion, entrants and winner (and their parent(s)/legal guardian(s) if entrants/winner are minors) agree to release, discharge and hold harmless the Promotion Parties from any and all damages whether direct or indirect, which may be due to or arise out of participation in the Promotion or any portion thereof, or the acceptance, use/misuse or possession of any Prize (or activity related thereto). As a condition of entering the Promotion, entrants and winner (and their parent(s)/legal guardian(s) if entrant/winner is a minor) agree that (1) under no circumstances will entrant and/or winner (or their parent(s)/legal guardian(s) if entrant/winner is a minor) be permitted to obtain awards for, and entrant and/or winner (or their parent(s)/legal guardian(s) if entrant/winner is a minor) hereby waives all rights to claim punitive, incidental, consequential or any other damages, and any claims, judgments or awards shall be limited to actual out-of-pocket expenses; (2) all causes of action arising out of or connected with this Promotion, or any Prize awarded, shall be resolved individually, without resort to any form of class action; and (3) in no event will any entrant and/or winner (or their parent(s)/legal guardian(s) if entrant/winner is a minor) be entitled to receive attorneys' fees. BY ENTERING THE PROMOTION, ENTRANTS AND/OR WINNER (AND THEIR PARENT(S)/LEGAL GUARDIAN(S) IF ENTRANT/WINNER IS A MINOR) AGREE TO RELEASE, INDEMNIFY AND HOLD HARMLESS PROMOTION PARTIES AND EACH OF THEIR RESPECTIVE PARENT, SUBSIDIARY AND AFFILIATED ENTITIES AS WELL AS THE SUCCESSORS, ASSIGNS AND LICENSEES OF EACH AND THE RESPECTIVE OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, AGENTS, EMPLOYEES, SHAREHOLDERS, CONTRACTORS AND REPRESENTATIVE OF EACH, FROM ANY AND ALL CLAIMS, EXPENSES, DAMAGES, (INCLUDING REASONABLE ATTORNEYS FEES), OR LIABILITY FOR ANY INJURY, LOSS, OR DAMAGE OF ANY KIND TO PERSONS (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, DEATH), AND PROPERTY, WHETHER DIRECT OR INDIRECT, WHICH MAY BE DUE TO OR ARISE OUT OF PARTICIPATION IN THE PROMOTION OR ANY PORTION THEREOF; A BREACH OR ALLEGATION WHICH IF TRUE WOULD CONSTITUTE A BREACH OF ANY OF ENTRANT'S AND/OR WINNER'S (AND THEIR PARENT(S)/LEGAL GUARDIAN(S) IF ENTRANT/WINNER IS A MINOR) REPRESENTATIONS, WARRANTIES OR OBLIGATIONS HEREIN; OR THE ACCEPTANCE, USE/MISUSE OR POSSESSION OF PRIZE(S), OR ANY PRIZE-RELATED ACTIVITY. ENTRANTS AND/OR WINNER (AND THEIR PARENT(S)/LEGAL GUARDIAN(S) IF ENTRANT/WINNER IS A MINOR) WAIVE ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.

**DISCLAIMER:** Promotion Parties are not responsible for printing or typographical errors in these Official Rules or in any Promotion-related materials. Sponsor reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to disqualify any individual that tampers with the entry process. Sponsor also reserves the right to terminate, suspend, cancel or modify the Promotion and award the Prize for the Promotion from among all eligible, non-suspect entries received (i) as of the date of termination or modification, as applicable, using the judging procedure outlined above and (ii) in a random drawing if for any reason this Promotion is not capable of running as planned due to any reason, including infection by computer virus, bugs, tampering, fraud, unauthorized intervention, technical failures or other causes that may corrupt or impair the integrity, fairness or proper play of the Promotion. Promotion Parties are not responsible or liable for any events which may cause errors and/or the Promotion to be stopped, including but not limited to any error, omission, interruption, deletion, defect, delay in operation or transmission, communications line failure, theft or destruction or unauthorized access to, or alteration of, entries, nor are they responsible for any problems or technical malfunction of any telephone, network or telephone lines, computer on-line systems, servers, or cable, satellite, or Internet Service Providers, computer equipment, mobile equipment, software or any other failure of any email or entry to be received by Sponsor on account of technical problems, human error or traffic congestion on the Internet or at any web site, or any combination thereof, including any injury or damage to entrant's or any other person's computer or mobile device relating to or resulting from participation in this Promotion or downloading any materials in this Promotion. Promotion Parties are not responsible for computer, mobile, mechanical, technical, electronic, network or other errors or problems, including any errors or problems that may occur in connection with the administration of the Promotion, the processing of entries, or in any other Promotion-related materials. The Promotion Parties may stop you from participating in this Promotion if you violate Official Rules or act, in Sponsor's sole discretion: (a) in a manner Sponsor determines to be not fair; (b) with an intent to annoy, threaten or harass any other entrant, winner or the Sponsor; or (c) in any other disruptive manner. Should more prizes be awarded through a computer, hardware, or software malfunction, error or failure, or for any other reason, in any prize category, than are stated for that category in the Official Rules, Sponsor reserves the right to award only the number of prizes stated in the Official Rules for that category. In no event will more prizes be awarded than that listed in Rule #3. 

**CAUTION: ANY ACT OR ATTEMPT BY AN ENTRANT AND/OR WINNER (OR THEIR PARENT(S)/LEGAL GUARDIAN(S) IF ENTRANT/WINNER IS A MINOR) TO DELIBERATELY DAMAGE ANY WEB SITE OR UNDERMINE THE LEGITIMATE OPERATION OF THIS PROMOTION IS A VIOLATION OF CRIMINAL AND CIVIL LAWS. SHOULD SUCH AN ATTEMPT BE MADE, PROMOTION PARTIES RESERVE THE RIGHT TO SEEK DAMAGES AND OTHER REMEDIES (INCLUDING ATTORNEYS' FEES) FROM ANY SUCH INDIVIDUAL(S) TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW.**

**CHOICE OF LAW AND JURISDICTION:** Except where prohibited, all issues and questions concerning the construction, validity, interpretation, and enforceability of these Official Rules, or the rights and obligations of entrants or winner, shall be governed by, and construed in accordance with, the laws of the Commonwealth of Massachusetts, without giving effect to any choice of law or conflict of law rules or provisions, which might otherwise cause the application of the laws of any jurisdiction other than the Commonwealth of Massachusetts. Any action seeking legal or equitable relief arising out of or relating to the Promotion or these Official Rules shall be brought only in the courts of the Commonwealth of Massachusetts. Entrants and/or winner (and their parent(s)/legal guardian(s) if entrant/winner is a minor) hereby irrevocably consent to the personal jurisdiction of said courts and waive any claim of forum non-convenience or lack of personal jurisdiction they may have. 

**WINNER'S LIST:** Entrants are responsible for complying with these Official Rules. To receive the winner's list for a specific Promotion, send a self-addressed stamped envelope to: Jossandmain.com Giveaway Winner List Request, c/o Joss and Main, 4 Copley Place, Floor 7, Boston, MA 02116. Please reference the dates of the Promotion Period and Prize with your request. 

**SPONSOR:** Wayfair LLC, 4 Copley Place, Floor 7, Boston, MA 02116 

Corporate Address:

4 Copley Place, Floor 7  
Boston, MA 02116  
USA  
(800) 632-8158
